xp-pen.com 2019-07-22

# Privacy Policy|XP-PEN

Privacy Policy

 **Our commitment to you**

This Privacy Policy sets out how XPPEN Technology CO. (“XP-Pen”) and its affiliated companies within the XPPEN Technology CO. (“XP-Pen”, “we”, “our” or “us”) collect, use, disclose, process and protect any information that you give us when you use our products, services located at www.xppen.com, and apps located at Google Play or Apple App Store. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using XP-Pen products, services and apps, it will only be used in accordance with this Privacy Policy and/or our terms and conditions for users.

The Privacy Policy is designed with you in mind, and it is important that you have a comprehensive understanding of our personal information collection and usage practices, as well as full confidence that ultimately, you have control of any personal information provided to XP-Pen.

In this Privacy Policy, “personal information” means information that can be used to identify an individual, either from that information alone or from that information combined with other information XP-Pen has access about that individual. Such personal information may include your name, address, and email address.

By using XP-Pen products and services, you are deemed to have read, acknowledged and accepted all the provisions stated here in the Privacy Policy, including any changes we may make from time to time. We are committed to protecting the privacy, confidentiality and security of your personal information by complying with applicable laws, including your local data protection legislation. We are equally committed to ensuring that all our employees and agents uphold these obligations.

Ultimately, what we want is the best for all our users. Should you have any concerns with our data handling practice as summarized in this Privacy Policy, please contact our Data Protection Officer at service@xp-pen.com to address your specific concerns. We will be happy to address them directly.

If you have questions or concerns regarding our Privacy Policy or practices, please contact us at service@xp-pen.com

 **What information is collected and how do we use it?**

 **Types of Information Collected**

In order to provide our services to you, we will ask you to provide personal information that is necessary to provide those services to you. If you do not provide your personal information, we may not be able to provide you with our products or services.

We may collect the following types of information (which may or may not be personal information):

Information you provide to us or upload (including your contact details): we may collect any and all personal information you provide to us, like your name, email address, information in relation to creating an account and participating in the XP-Pen Forum or other XP-Pen platforms, email address you insert into your contacts or to send a message, feedback, and any other information you provide us.

Information specific to you that may be assigned by us: we may collect and use information.

Location information (only for specific services/functionalities): various types of information on your location. For example, country code, city code, mobile network code, cell identity, longitude and latitude information, language settings.

Log information: information related to your use of certain functions, apps and websites. For example, cookies and other anonymous identifier technologies, IP addresses, temporary message history, standard system logs.

Other information: environmental characteristics value (ECV) (i.e. value generated from XP-Pen Account ID, phone device ID, connected wi-fi ID and location value)

 **How the personal information is used & How the personal information is used under GDPR. **

If our processing of your information is subject to the General Data Protection Regulation 2016/679 (“GDPR”), we use your information according to the following lawful bases for processing. The examples are for sake of clarity, but not by way of limitation, to the other statements made regarding processing of data in this Privacy Policy. 

Personal information is collected for providing services and / or products to you, and legal compliance on our part under applicable laws. You hereby consent that we may process and disclose personal information to our affiliated companies (which are in the communications, social media, technology and cloud businesses), Third Party Service Providers (defined below) for the purposes stated in this Privacy Policy.

 **We may use your personal information for the following purposes:**

Providing, processing, maintaining, improving and developing our goods and/or services to you, including after-sales and customer support and for services on your device or through our websites

Communicating with you about your device, service or any general queries, such as updates, customer inquiry support, information about our events, notices.

Conducting marketing related activities, such as providing marketing and promotional materials and updates. For more information on marketing and promotional activities, please refer to the Direct Marketing section below.

Allowing you to post comments in public forums.

Conducting promotional activities, such as sweepstakes and Facebook events.

Analysing and developing statistical information on use of our products and services to better improve our products and services.

Storing and maintaining information about you for our business operations or legal obligations

Here are more details on how we use your information (which may include personal information)

Setting up your XP-Pen Account. Personal information collected when creating a XP-Pen Account on our web sites or through our mobile devices is used for creating the personal XP-Pen Account and profile page for the user.

Allowing you to participate in XP-Pen Forum. Personal information in relation to the XP-Pen Forum or other XP-Pen Internet platforms may be used for profile page display, interaction with other users, participating in the forum.

Collecting user feedback. The feedback you choose to provide is valuable in helping XP-Pen make improvements to our services. In order to follow up on the feedback you have chosen to provide, XP-Pen may correspond with you using the personal information that you have provided and keep records.

Sending notices. From time to time, we may use your personal information to send important notices, such as communications about purchases and changes to our terms, conditions, and policies.

Direct Marketing

We may use your name, and email address, XP-Pen Account ID to provide marketing materials to you relating to goods and services of XP-Pen companies and our business partners which offer network, mobile applications and cloud products and services. To provide better user experience, we may recommend above-mentioned products, services and activities based on information about your website browsing history, birthday, age, gender, and location. We will only to use your personal data after we have obtained your consent or indication of no objection in accordance with local data protection laws, which may require separate explicit consent. You have the right to opt out of our proposed use of your personal data for direct marketing. If you no longer wish to receive certain types of email communications you may opt-out by following the unsubscribe link located at the bottom of each communication. We will not transfer your personal data to our business partners for use by our business partners in direct marketing.

Cookies and Other Technologies (only when browsing www.xppen.com)

What information is collected and how do we use them? Technologies such as cookies, tags, and scripts are used by XP-Pen and our Third Party Service Providers. These technologies are used in analyzing trends, administering the site, tracking users’ movements around the website and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We may receive reports based on the use of these technologies by these companies on an individual as well as aggregated basis.

Log Files: As true of most websites, we gather certain information and store it in log files. This information may include Internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and/or clickstream data. We do not link this automatically collected data to other information we gather about you.

Advertising: We partner with our Third Party Service Providers to either display advertising on our website or to manage our advertising on other sites. Our Third Party Service Provider may use technologies such as cookies to gather information about your activities on this site and other sites in order to provide you advertising based upon your browsing activities and interests. 

**Who do we share your information with?**

We do not sell any personal information to third parties.

We may disclose your personal information on occasion to third parties (as described below) in order to provide the products or services that you have requested.

Disclosure may be made to Third Party Service Providers and affiliated companies listed in this section below. In each case described in this section, you can be assured that XP-Pen will only share your personal information in accordance with your consent. You should know that when XP-Pen shares your personal information with a Third Party Service Provider under any circumstance described in this section, XP-Pen will contractually specify that the third party is subject to practices and obligations to comply with applicable local data protection laws. XP-Pen will contractually ensure compliance by any Third Party Service Providers with the privacy standards that apply to them in your home jurisdiction.

Sharing with our Group and Third Party Service Providers

From time to time, in order to conduct business operations smoothly in providing you with the full capabilities of our products and services, we may disclose your personal information from time to time to other XP-Pen affiliated companies (in communications, social media, technology or cloud businesses), or our third party service providers which are our mailing houses, delivery service providers, telecommunications companies, data centres, data storage facilities, customer service providers, advertising and marketing service providers, agents acting on behalf of XP-Pen, [related corporations, and/or other third parties] (together “Third Party Service Providers”). Such Third Party Service Providers would be processing your personal information on XP-Pen’s behalf or for one or more of the purposes listed above. 

Sharing with Others

XP-Pen may disclose your personal information without further consent when required under applicable law.

 **Information Not Requiring Consent**

We may share anonymised information and statistics in aggregate form with third parties for business purposes, for example with advertisers on our website, we may share them trends about the general use of our services, such as the number of customers in certain demographic groups who purchased certain products or who carried out certain transactions.

For the avoidance of doubt, XP-Pen may collect, use or disclose your personal information without your consent if it is and only to the extent it is allowed explicitly under local data protection laws, such as to comply with a subpoena, and when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request.

Security Safeguards

 **XP-Pen’s Security Measures**

We are committed to ensuring that your personal information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access, disclosure or other similar risks, we have put in place reasonable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect on XP-Pen websites. We will use all reasonable efforts to safeguard your personal information.

All your personal information is stored on secure servers that are protected in controlled facilities. We classify your data based on importance and sensitivity, and ensure that your personal information has the highest security level. We make sure that our employees and Third Party Service Providers who access the information to help provide you with our products and services are subject to strict contractual confidentiality obligations and may be disciplined or terminated if they fail to meet such obligations. We have special access controls for cloud based data storage as well. All in all, we regularly review our information collection, storage and processing practices, including physical security measures, to guard against any unauthorized access and use.

We will take all practicable steps to safeguard your personal information. However, you should be aware that the use of the Internet is not entirely secure, and for this reason we cannot guarantee the security or integrity of any personal information which is transferred from you or to you via the Internet.

 **What you can do!**

You can play your part in safeguarding your personal information by not disclosing your login password or account information to anybody unless such person is duly authorized by you. Whenever you log in as a XP-Pen Account user on XP-Pen websites, particularly on somebody else's computer or on public Internet terminals, you should always log out at the end of your session.

XP-Pen cannot be held responsible for lapses in security caused by third party accesses to your personal information as a result of your failure to keep your personal information private. Notwithstanding the foregoing, you must notify us immediately if there is any unauthorized use of your account by any other Internet user or any other breach of security.

Your assistance will help us protect the privacy of your personal information.

Retention Policy

Personal information will be held for as long as it is necessary to fulfill the purpose for which it was collected, or as required or permitted by applicable laws. We shall cease to retain personal information, or remove the means by which the personal information can be associated with particular individuals, as soon as it is reasonable to assume that the purpose for which that personal information was collected is no longer being served by retention of the personal information and retention is no longer necessary for legal, resolve disputes, enforce our agreements or other business purposes.

Accessing other Features on your Device

 **You have control over your information!**

Controlling settings

XP-Pen recognizes that privacy concerns differ from person to person. Therefore, we provide examples of ways XP-Pen makes available for you to choose to restrict the collection, use, disclosure or processing of your personal information and control your privacy settings:

Toggle on/off for the User Experience Program and Location Access functions

Log in and out of the XP-Pen Account

Toggle on/off for other services and functionalities which deal with sensitive or personal information

If you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for the above mentioned purposes, you may change your mind at any time by writing or emailing us at service@xp-pen.com 

Access, Updating or Correcting Your Personal Information

You have the right to request access to and/or correction of any other personal information that we hold about you. When you update your personal information, you will be asked to verify your identity before we proceed with your request. Once we obtain sufficient information to accommodate your request for access to or correction of your personal information, we shall proceed to respond to your request within any time frame set out under your applicable data protection laws.

We normally provide such services for free but reserve the right to charge a reasonable fee for your data access request.

If you would like to request access to your personal data held by us or if you believe any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible at the email address below. Email: service@xp-pen.com 

XP-Pen may use overseas facilities operated and controlled by XP-Pen to process or back up your personal information. Currently, XP-Pen has data centres in United States, Taiwan and China. These overseas jurisdictions may or may not have in place data protection laws which are substantially similar to that in your home jurisdiction. We may transfer to and store your personal information at our overseas facilities. However, this does not change any of our commitments to safeguard your personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

Miscellaneous

Minors

We consider it the responsibility of parents to monitor their children’s use of our products and services. Nevertheless, it is our policy not to require personal information from minors or offer to send any promotional materials to persons in that category.

XP-Pen does not seek or intend to seek to receive any personal information from minors. Should a parent or guardian have reasons to believe that a minor has provided XP-Pen with personal information without their prior consent, please contact us to ensure that the personal information is removed and the minor unsubscribes from any of the applicable XP-Pen services.

Order of Precedence

If you have agreed to our applicable User Agreements, in the event of inconsistency between such User Agreements and this Privacy Policy, such User Agreements shall prevail.

Governing Law

We do not represent or warrant that this Privacy Policy complies with the privacy laws of any jurisdiction and accordingly, you shall not construe this Privacy Policy as such.

Updates To The Privacy Policy

We keep our Privacy Policy under regular review and may update this privacy policy to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make material changes to our Privacy Policy, we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or post the changes on all the XP-Pen websites , so that you may be aware of the information we collect and how we use it. Such changes to our Privacy Policy shall apply from the effective date as set out in the notice or on the website. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices. Your continued use of products and services on the websites, mobile phones and/or any other device will be taken as acceptance of the updated Privacy Policy. We will seek your fresh consent before we collect more personal information from you or when we wish to use or disclose your personal information for new purposes.

Do I have to agree to any third party terms and conditions?

Our Privacy Policy does not apply to products and services offered by a third party. XP-Pen products and services may include third parties’ products, services and links to third parties’ websites. When you use such products or services, they may collect your information too. For this reason, we strongly suggest that you read the third party’s privacy policy as you have taken time to read ours. We are not responsible for and cannot control how third parties use personal information which they collect from you. Our Privacy Policy does not apply to other sites linked from our services.

Here are third party terms and privacy policies that apply when you use these specific products:

Social Media (Features) and Widgets

Our websites include social media features, such as the Facebook Like button and Widgets, such as the Share this button or interactive mini-programs that run on our site. These features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social media features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our websites. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.

Single Sign-On

Depending on your jurisdiction, you may be able to log in to our website using sign-on services such as Facebook Connect or an Open ID provider. These services will authenticate your identity, provide you the option to share certain personal information (such as your name and email address) with us, and to pre-populate our sign up form. Services like Facebook Connect give you the option to post information about your activities on this website to your profile page to share with others within your network.

 **Contact XP-Pen**

To make a claim under this Privacy, contact XP-Pen at:

WEBSITE: http://www.xp-pen.com/

EMAIL: service@xp-pen.com

CALL CENTER: +1 657-445-6129

* This contact information may change without notice. Please contact your authorized XP-Pen retailer for updated contact information.
